Contact

ronaldravengarcia@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ronald-ravengarcia-b8477716a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Technical Support
Data Analysis
Data Entry

Ronald Raven Garcia

IT Staff at TERP Asia Construction Corporation

Metro Manila, National Capital Region, Philippines

Summary

Self-motivated and enthusiastic worker with work experience from different industries. Confident, hard-working, and committed to seeing results in whatever position I am in. Reliable and dedicated to finding a place that will benefit from my skill-set and energetic drive.

Experience

TERP ASIA CONSTRUCTION CORPORATION

IT Staff

October 2022 - Present (8 months)

Starlite Ferries, Inc.

Deck Cadet

August 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 2 months)

TaskUs

Customer Support Representative April 2018 - August 2018 (5 months)

NCR - National Capital Region, Philippines

Education

Technological Institute of the Philippines

Bachelor of Science - BS, Marine Transportation · (2014 - 2018)

Uplift Code Camp

Full Stack Web Development · (May 2023)

San Beda College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Psychology · (2012 - 2013)